&gt；&gt；steve kinney：这里有一个问题，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: There is a issue here,
right?
我只需要解决这个问题，因为我在保持我的状态在领域，对吗？
I only had to solve this problem because
I was keeping my state in the dom, right?
在我可以变异之前，我必须去测量它。
I had to go measure stuff
before I could mutate it.
我不再将我的数据保存在dom中，我写的是棱角或余烬或反应。
I don't keep my data in the dom anymore,
I write angular or ember or react.
我把东西保持在状态，对吧？
I keep things in state, right?
例如，你可以把一些像这样的组件放在一起
So you could for instance put together
some kind of component like this which
保持跟踪，这是一半的组件，这是我可以放在屏幕上的东西。
keeps track and this is a half component,
it's what I could fit on a screen.
我将保留我所有宽度的数组。
I'm gonna keep an array
of all of my width.
我要在这里的页面下面拍摄他们
I'm gonna shoot them under
the page over here and
然后我只需将这些数字翻倍并重新渲染。
then I will just double those numbers and
re-render.
在此之前，您将不必阅读dom和
Before you would not have
to read from the dom and
如果不从dom中阅读，你可以想写多少就写多少。
if don't read from the dom you
can write as much as you want.
你永远不会有布局垃圾的问题，
You're never gonna have
a layout trashing issue,
从来不是一个强有力的词，因为我给你看了一个，它是在反应中，但通常
never is a strong word cuz I showed you
one, it was in react, but generally
说这个非常孤立的事件，应该可以解决我们所有的问题，对吧？
speaking this very isolated incident that
should solve all of our problems, right?
所以让我们看看会发生什么，结果是我用这个React应用程序运行了一个React
So lets see what happens, it turns out I
have a React running with this React app
跑步，还有同样的事情在进行。
running, with the same thing going on.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我们可以测量它，我们可以比较差异。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And we can measure it,
we can compare the differences.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：那就去录制吧。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So
go ahead, do a recording.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：你可以看到，哇，这有点奇怪。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And you can see that,
wow, this is kinda weird.
这里发生了很多事情。
There's a lot of stuff happening in here.
那可不好。
That's not great.
我告诉过你可以在用户计时API中获得反应信息。
I told you you can get React
information in the user timing API.
所以你可以看到，这是协调反应树和应用程序更新，
So you can see, this is reconciling
the React tree and an app update,
等等，对吧？
so on and so forth, right?
这里发生了很多事情，57毫秒不是很好
There's a lot of stuff happening here and
57 milliseconds isn't great for
换了一堆酒吧。
changing a bunch of bars.
但事实证明我做的是最糟糕的事之一
But it turns out that I am
committing one of the worst
Web性能中的犯罪，也就是，我在开发模式中使用REACT
crimes in web performance which is,
I'm using React in development mode and
期望生产级别的性能。
expecting production level performance.
React做了一大堆事情
React does a bunch of stuff.
我之前告诉过你，测量需要时间。
I told you before, measuring takes time.
所以React在开发模式下做了一大堆事情
So React is doing a whole bunch
of stuff in development mode
给你这些漂亮的东西并管理一大堆东西。
to give you these pretty things and
manage a whole bunch of stuff.
检查道具类型和所有这些东西，这些东西很慢。
And checking prop types and
all these things and that stuff is slow.
因此，如果您有React Developer工具，有时您可以看到一个页面
And so if you have the React developer
tools sometimes you can see a page
如果在生产模式下使用REACT，则这将是黑色的
where this will be black if it's
using React in production mode and
如果在开发模式中使用，它将会像可怕的橙色一样。
it will be this like scary orange
if it's used in development mode.
就像保持这样的乐趣一样，
As fun to like keep that going,
只需访问仍在开发模式下运行的站点即可。
just go visit sites that are still
running in development mode.
我是说，有时候我觉得
I mean, and it's like one of
the things sometimes I think
说他们是故意的，我的意思是如果他们说了，那就意味着他们知道这件事
says they do it on purpose I mean if they
say it, that means they know about it and
他们决定现在这是他们的新状态。
they've decided that that's
now their new state.
对，有些网站完全是偶然的，有时候就像不知道
Right, some websites are totally doing it
by accident sometimes it's like don't know
关于它，有时就像有人试图改变webpack的构建和
about it and sometimes it's like somebody
tried to change the webpack build and
现在我们意外地发布了开发代码，对吗？
now we're accidentally shipping
the development code, right?
这种情况已经在我的应用程序上发生过几次了。
This has happened to my app a few times.
所以这真的很有帮助。
So this is really helpful.
结果是57毫秒我们正在做所有这些额外的事情。
So it turns out 57 milliseconds
we're doing all of this extra stuff.
这不是很好，对吧？
That's not great, right?
所以让它处于开发模式是次优的。
So having it in development
mode is suboptimal.
让我们实际比较一下它看起来是什么样子，因为事实证明我
Let's actually compare what that looks
like though, because it turns out that I
在该存储库中也有此应用程序的一个版本，该版本是为构建的
also have a version of this app in
that repository that is built for
生产方式。
production mode.
所以让我们继续，实际上，
So let's go ahead and actually,
我应该把它放在这里。
I should have it over here.
同样的申请，我们再录一遍。
Same application, let's record it again.
哇，这样好多了，对吧？
Wow, that's much better right?
这是.让我们比较和对比。
That's...let's compare and contrast.
巨大的悲伤黄色穗状物。
Giant spike of sad yellow.
小肿块。
Little bump.
好吧，简单的事实是处于开发模式
Alright, the simple fact of
being in development mode
与生产模式有很大的不同。
is a huge difference
versus production mode.
好的，现在你可以看到这里仍然有很多事情发生。
Right, now you can see there's still
a bunch of stuff happening here.
这又是永恒的交易
And this is again the eternal trade for
当涉及到使用框架时的性能，对吧。
performance when it comes to
using a framework, right.
框架将在很多时候为您做出决策。
The framework is gonna make
decisions a lot of the time for you.
它使您更容易使您的状态远离转储，就像帮助
It make it easier to keep your state
out of the dump which like helps
您可以避免布局垃圾。
you avoid layout trashing.
他们喜欢为你批处理所有转储的东西，但他们是JavaScript代码和
They like batch all your dump things for
you but they are JavaScript code and
他们承担了一定数量的开销，对吗？
they take a certain
amount of overhead Right?
这永远是你需要做的权衡。
And that is always
the tradeoff you need to make.
我的信仰体系通常是这样的，特别是如果你有一个团队和
I am of the belief system that generally,
especially if you have a team and
你有广泛的经验，你试图推出产品
you have a wide range of experiences and
you're trying to get product out
使用框架的成本对你有益的门，对吗？
the door that the cost of using
a framework is beneficial for you, right?
但如果你有一堆
But if you had a bunch of,
如果你坐在那里，真的想微调你的应用程序，
if you sat there and really wanted
to fine tune your application,
手工制作的应用程序可能会更快，但可能不值得。
hand-crafted application will probably be
faster But like, probably not worth it.
但是，是的，你可以看到有一些开销。
But yeah,
you can see there is some overhead.
但你可以看到，我们仍然在大约9.3毫秒。
But you can see that we're still at like,
9.3 milaseconds.
我把这叫做胜利，对吧？
I'm gonna call this a win, right?
这只是一些需要考虑和考虑的事情。
It's just something to consider and
something to think about.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：所以是的。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So yeah.
友好的事实是，生产模式在反应中很重要。
Friendly fact,
production mode is important in React.
我还有一张幻灯片稍后会再说一遍，
I have another slide that's
gonna say this again later,
因为我真的犯过很多次这样的错误。
because I've literally made
this mistake multiple times.
所以我觉得如果我不断重复我自己，你会想一想。
So I feel like if I keep repeating myself,
you will think about it.
如果你不写REACTION，可能会有这样的版本
And if you don't write React,
there's probably a version of this for
你的申请绝对值得一查。
your application and
is definitely worth checking.
因为有一个9.3毫秒的戏剧性变化。
Cuz there was a dramatic
change of 9.3 milliseconds.
我想第一件事是什么，但是
I figured what the first thing was, but
那张图上的时间要长得多，悲伤也多得多。
it was a lot longer with a lot
more sadness in that graph.
所以一定要确保你使用的是生产模式，不管它是什么。
So definitely make sure you're using
production mode for whatever it is.
好的，酷。
All right, cool.
So&gt；&gt；steve kinney：so
So
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So
它不是，反应能帮你解决问题吗？
it doesn't,
does React solve your problems for you?
对吧？也许，也许不是，对吧？
Right?
Maybe, maybe not, right?
你仍然可以看到我之前展示的幻灯片
You can still see that slide that
I showed earlier where I have
一个React应用程序仍然有这个问题。
a React app that still has this problem.
它不会让你一路走到那里。
It's not gonna get you all the way there.
有一个框架是有帮助的，你仍然需要留心。
Having a framework is helpful,
you still need to be mindful.
你还需要测量。
You still need to measure.
是的，这些事情仍然可能发生。
Right and these things can still happen.
我猜你的问题是你想的是什么
I assume with your question you're
thinking about like what was
这个问题的答案。
the answer to this.
我还不知道。
I don't know yet.
我还没挖进去。
I haven't dug in.
[笑]但是看起来我在简单的拖拽上有几个小问题
[LAUGHS] But looks like I've got a few
little issues here on the simple drag
放入按钮，就像我测量了它，现在我可以继续并修复它。
in and drop in button and like I measured
it and now I can go ahead and fix it.
所以这里的关键要点是不要混合读取布局属性和编写它们，
So kinda key takeaways here are don't mix
reading layout properties and write them,
你会做不必要的工作。
you'll do unnecessary work.
另外，如果您可以通过添加CSS类来更改某些内容，
Also, if you can just change
something by adding a CSS class,
有点像回到那种风格的计算，我们根本不读那个。
kinda going back to that style
calculation, we don't read that at all.
这一个，我们想要加倍一堆单独的酒吧。
This one, we want to double up
a bunch of individual bars.
但是只要添加一个类，就会导致一次回流，但是
But with just adding a class,
you will cause one reflow, but
你没有办法让自己进入那个循环。
there's no way that you can
get yourself into that loop.
因此，如果您可以通过拥有一个CSS类来处理这个问题，该类的第二个状态是
So, if you can handle this by just having
a CSS class that has the second state that
你想和尝试手工做和计算每件事相比，去做吧。
you want versus trying to do it by hand
and calculating everything, go for that.
对你来说，这永远是更安全的选择。
That is always going to be
the safer option for you.
在存储数据和存储器时，无论它是在REACT中，2i将它存储在状态中，
In storing data and memory, whether
it's in react,2I stored it in the state,
在这种情况下，我之前给你看过。
in that case I showed you earlier.
但就像，你知道，你可以很容易地把它放在内存中的某个地方，如果
But like, you know, you could easily just
keep it in array somewhere in memory if
你是用手做的。
you were doing this by hand.
没有反应，棱角分明，还有Ember，都是用JavaScript写的，对吧？
There's nothing React, and Angular, and
Ember, all written in JavaScript, right?
使用这些框架可以做的任何事情，都可以自己做。
Anything you can do with those frameworks,
you could do on your own.
例如，将所有这些宽度保留在一个数组中
Like, keeping all those widths in an array
可能比一开始就把他们留在世界上更聪明，对吧？
was probably smarter than keeping
them in the dom to begin with, right?
这并不总是你可以选择的，对吧？
That's not always an option that you have,
right?
就像，当我编辑用户内容时，对吧，
Like, when I'm editing user content,
right,
我并不总是那么奢侈，对吧？
I don't always have that luxury, right?
所以无论哪种方式都要记住这一点。
So it's something to
keep in mind either way.
你不需要一个框架。
You don't need a framework.
你仍然可以做坏事，如果你有一个框架，就像我给你展示的那样。
You can do bad things still,
if you have a framework, as I showed you.
我对此感到内疚。
I'm guilty of it.
最后，主要的一点是你可能甚至不知道你的布局
And finally, the major point is you
might not even know that you're layout
打，因为我没有，直到我去拍那个截图。
thrashing, cuz I didn't until I
went to take that screenshot.
这有点像这个故事的寓意。
That's kinda like the moral of the story.